[
   {
      "front":"caption",
      "back":"Bildunterschrift"
   },
   {
      "front":"governor",
      "back":"Gouverneur/in"
   },
   {
      "front":"migrant worker",
      "back":"Wanderarbeiter"
   },
   {
      "front":"homeless",
      "back":"obdachlos"
   },
   {
      "front":"admire",
      "back":"bewundern"
   },
   {
      "front":"creative",
      "back":"kreativ, einfallsreich"
   },
   {
      "front":"innovation",
      "back":"Innovation, Neuerung"
   },
   {
      "front":"wave",
      "back":"Welle"
   },
   {
      "front":"wildfire",
      "back":"Wasld-, Buschbrand"
   },
   {
      "front":"wildlife",
      "back":"Tierwelt; frei lebende Tiere"
   },
   {
      "front":"majority",
      "back":"Mehrheit"
   },
   {
      "front":"minorety",
      "back":"Minderheit"
   },
   {
      "front":"fewer",
      "back":"weniger"
   },
   {
      "front":"attitude to/torwards",
      "back":"Haltung gegenüber;\nEinstellung zu"
   },
   {
      "front":"comment",
      "back":"Kommentar"
   },
   {
      "front":"useless",
      "back":"nutzlos, unfähig"
   },
   {
      "front":"education",
      "back":"(Schul-, Aus-)Bildung; Erziehung"
   }
]